Vatthana Boulom

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ACCELERATOR STUDENT

Profile

Hi, I'm Vatthana, currently Executive Pastry Chef. Hoping to extend my knowledge in coding and start my tech career with the help of Mission Ready HQ! I'm excited about the experience your accelerator program will give me and look forward to starting this thrilling Journey with you!

Employment History

Executive Pastry Chef, La Petite Fourchette & Copain Bakery, Auckland

APRIL 2018 - PRESENT

- Developing both companies since their opening. La Petite Fourchette in 2018
 & Copain in 2022.
- Expanding the business opportunities through Wholesale, Catering, Store, and events offers.
- Creating various menus with local and seasonal products.
- Solving every day's customer problems and requests.
- Adapting workflow to the company's needs.
- Responding to the company objective by regulating food and staff cost.
- Maintaining the kitchen and surrounding areas in conditions that meet the company standards and health code regulations.
- Building and leading two teams of up to 5 people each.
- Hiring, training, and supervising kitchen staff.
- Monitoring inventory and purchasing supplies and food from approved vendors.
- Sustaining a healthy work environment for both kitchen and front-of-house employees.

Pastry Demi-chef de partie, The Peninsula Paris - 5 Star Palace Hotel, Paris, France

DECEMBER 2016 - FEBRUARY 2018

- Pastry section Production for Gastronomic restaurant, tea time, bar, function, and
 - brasserie.
- Stock control and inventory on a weekly basis.
- Proven reliability, responsible and innovative approach to work.
- Management of 3 commis and 2 interns.
- Worked in a team of 15 Pastry chef

Pastry Apprentice and Pastry Commis, Restaurant Yannick Alléno Paris - 3 Michelin Star - 31st Best restaurant in the world "2016", Paris, France

AUGUST 2014 - DECEMBER 2015

- Chef Yannick Alleno: Best chef of the year 2015 " Gault & Millau"
- Pastry Chef Aurelien Rivoire Best PAstry chef of the year 2021 " Gault & Millau
- Pastry section Production for Gastronomic restaurant
- Function's Production

Details

1/43 Dickens Street
Auckland, 1021
New Zealand
+6421374018
boulom.vatthana@gmail.com

......

French

DATE OF BIRT 20/08/1994

Skills

Active Listening

Teamwork Skills

Fast Learner

HTML5

Python

CSS

Hobbies

Anything Tech related Scuba diving Water Sports Reading

Languages

French

English

- In charge of the restaurant's service
- Worked in a team of 10 people

Pastry Apprentice, Hotel Du Collectionneur Paris - 5 Star Hotel, Paris, France

APRIL 2014 - AUGUST 2015

- In charge of the restaurant service
- Banquet Production
- Worked in a team of 5 people

Pastry Apprentice, Restaurant Francois Gagnaire - 1 Michelin Star, Le Puy en Velay, France

AUGUST 2013 - MARCH 2014

- Gastronomic pastry production
- In charge of the restaurant service
- · worked in a team of 10 people

Education

CAP pâtisserie, Ecole hôtelière de Paris, Paris, France

2013 - 2015

MC Desserts de restaurants, Ecole hôtelière de Paris, Paris, France

2015 - 2016

Courses

100 Days of Code: The Complete Python Pro Bootcamp for 2023, The app Brewery - Udemy

OCTOBER 2022 - PRESENT

The Complete 2023 Web Development Bootcamp, The app Brewery - Udemy

APRIL 2023

Master the Coding Interview: Data Structures + Algorithms, Zero To Mastery - Udemy

MARCH 2023

Note about the courses

The courses above are all the materials I hope to achieve as a base foundation for my future learning with MRHQ. (October 2023)